Office of Student Services, School of Dental Medicine Records UA235
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Post Graduate files, 1948 -- 2018; UA235.002; 42.5 Linear Feet
  - Bennett, Gordon G., 1968; UA235.002.052.00002 (Box 52)
  - Beratis, Harry, 1965; UA235.002.052.00003 (Box 52)
  - Berg, Ehud, 1992; UA235.002.052.00004 (Box 52)
  - Bergstein, Jack, 1953; UA235.002.052.00005 (Box 52)
  - Berini, Alessandro, 1989; UA235.002.052.00006 (Box 52)
  - Berkman, Milton D., 1968; UA235.002.052.00007 (Box 52)
  - Berlucchi, Ignazio, 1996; UA235.002.052.00008 (Box 52)
  - Bernbach, Alan L., 1977; UA235.002.052.00009 (Box 52)
  - Bernstein, Bruce A., 1971; UA235.002.052.00010 (Box 52)
  - Bernstein, Murray, 1951; UA235.002.052.00011 (Box 52)
  - Bershon, James S., 1972; UA235.002.052.00012 (Box 52)
  - Berte, Joseph J., 1970; UA235.002.052.00013 (Box 52)
  - Bessler, Barry, 1998; UA235.002.052.00014 (Box 52)
  - Bezanson, Richard H., 1983; UA235.002.052.00015 (Box 52)
  - Bhargaua, Kashyap, 1958; UA235.002.052.00016 (Box 52)
  - Bhiladvala, Pallonji, 1959; UA235.002.052.00017 (Box 52)
  - Biebuyck, Jean-Marie, 1988; UA235.002.052.00018 (Box 52)
  - Bilder, Barbara, 1977; UA235.002.052.00019 (Box 52)
  - Bilous, Oresta L., 1999; UA235.002.052.00020 (Box 52)
  - Bilionis, Angelo, 1962; UA235.002.052.00021 (Box 52)
  - Binder, Arnold E., 1954; UA235.002.052.00022 (Box 52)
  - Bissell, Robert G., 1972; UA235.002.052.00023 (Box 52)
  - Bissell, Ronald D., 1972; UA235.002.052.00024 (Box 52)
  - Bjornson, Thomas, 2003; UA235.002.052.00025 (Box 52)
  - Blackstone, Donald, 1991; UA235.002.052.00026 (Box 52)
  - Blackstone, Gregory, 1984; UA235.002.052.00027 (Box 52)
  - Blaser, Herbert R., 1973; UA235.002.052.00028 (Box 52)
  - Bloom, Richard, 1975; UA235.002.052.00029 (Box 52)
  - Blumenfield, Walter L., 1969; UA235.002.052.00030 (Box 52)
  - Blunt, Matthew H., 1969; UA235.002.052.00031 (Box 52)
  - Buck, James L., 1952; UA235.002.052.00032 (Box 52)
  - Bock, Joseph Jr., 1971; UA235.002.052.00033 (Box 52)
  - Bogis, John, 1979; UA235.002.052.00034 (Box 52)
  - Boke, Bruce Ray, 1970; UA235.002.052.00035 (Box 52)
  - Bonacci, Fred, 2006; UA235.002.052.00036 (Box 52)
  - Bongiorno, Alfred Michael, 1978; UA235.002.052.00037 (Box 52)
  - Bongiovanni, Carol T., 1993; UA235.002.052.00038 (Box 52)
  - Bonner, John Walter, 1986; UA235.002.052.00039 (Box 52)
  - Booth, Donald F., 1964; UA235.002.052.00040 (Box 52)
  - Boroumand, Jahansah, 1978; UA235.002.052.00041 (Box 52)
  - Borzangy, Abdul Rahman, 1996; UA235.002.052.00042 (Box 52)
  - Boustany, Farid, 1981; UA235.002.052.00043 (Box 52)
  - Bowman, John F., 1954; UA235.002.052.00044 (Box 52)
  - Boyd, Keith E., 1984; UA235.002.052.00045 (Box 52)
  - Boyd, Tobin T., 1973; UA235.002.052.00046 (Box 52)
  - Boyles, Emmett L., 1959; UA235.002.052.00047 (Box 52)
  - Bradford, Blair, 2004; UA235.002.052.00048 (Box 52)
  - Branca, Richard Wayne, 1969; UA235.002.052.00049 (Box 52)
  - Branch, Fayette H. Jr., 1950; UA235.002.052.00050 (Box 52)
  - Braseth, Peter C., 1982; UA235.002.052.00051 (Box 52)
  - Braun, Robert B., 1958; UA235.002.052.00052 (Box 52)
  - Braun, Thomas F., 1983; UA235.002.052.00053 (Box 52)
  - Braverman, Martin, 1984; UA235.002.052.00054 (Box 52)
  - Bravman, Richard, 1983; UA235.002.052.00055 (Box 52)
  - Brayton, Stephan M., 1972; UA235.002.052.00056 (Box 52)
  - Brehm, Harold L., 1956; UA235.002.052.00057 (Box 52)
  - Breitbart, Allan, 1961; UA235.002.052.00058 (Box 52)
  - Brendlinger, Darwin Lamar, 1968; UA235.002.052.00059 (Box 52)
  - Brenner, Lawrence Richard, 1964; UA235.002.052.00060 (Box 52)
  - Bress, Charles, 1962; UA235.002.052.00061 (Box 52)
  - Brion, Andree M., 1968; UA235.002.052.00062 (Box 52)
  - Briss, Barry S., 1970; UA235.002.052.00063 (Box 52)
  - Briss, David S., 1995; UA235.002.052.00064 (Box 52)
  - Broccoli, Anthony C., 1987; UA235.002.052.00065 (Box 52)
  - Brockman, Melvin, 1964; UA235.002.052.00066 (Box 52)
  - Broderick, John G., 1996; UA235.002.052.00067 (Box 52)
  - Brog, Blake, 1982; UA235.002.052.00068 (Box 52)
  - Bronsky, Donald, 1958; UA235.002.052.00069 (Box 52)
  - Brown, Jerome, 1975; UA235.002.052.00070 (Box 52)
  - Brugnami, Federico, 1992; UA235.002.052.00071 (Box 52)
  - Bruner, Hugh H. Jr., 1968; UA235.002.052.00072 (Box 52)
  - Bryan, James Eugene, 1952; UA235.002.052.00073 (Box 52)
  - Buchan, Walter A., 1985; UA235.002.052.00074 (Box 52)
  - Buchanan, Bruce P., 1971; UA235.002.052.00075 (Box 52)
  - Buck, Irwin, 1951; UA235.002.052.00076 (Box 52)
  - Bukai, Firas O., 1993; UA235.002.052.00077 (Box 52)
  - Bustillo, Carla, 1998; UA235.002.052.00078 (Box 52)
  - Bucken, Patricia I., 1982; UA235.002.052.00079 (Box 52)
  - Bulchak, Walter, 1963; UA235.002.052.00080 (Box 52)
  - Bullock, John E., 1973; UA235.002.052.00081 (Box 52)
  - Bunnen, Robert L., 1956; UA235.002.052.00082 (Box 52)
  - Bunyasiri, Chongmas, 1955; UA235.002.052.00083 (Box 52)
  - Buono, Robert David, 1965; UA235.002.052.00084 (Box 52)
  - Burk, Greg A., 1983; UA235.002.052.00085 (Box 52)
  - Busciglio, John A., 1972; UA235.002.052.00086 (Box 52)
  - Butler, David, 2004; UA235.002.052.00087 (Box 52)
  - Cabeceiras, David, 1983; UA235.002.052.00088 (Box 52)
  - Cabral, Ema M., 1995; UA235.002.052.00089 (Box 52)
  - Cabrera, Philip, 1993; UA235.002.052.00090 (Box 52)
  - Caiazzo, Alfonso, 1997; UA235.002.052.00091 (Box 52)
  - Cahoon, Michael, 1980; UA235.002.053.00001 (Box 53)
  - Cail, Allen R., 1966; UA235.002.053.00002 (Box 53)
  - Caldwell, Mirna Armaleh, 2001; UA235.002.053.00003 (Box 53)
  - Caldwell, Robert, 2003; UA235.002.053.00004 (Box 53)
  - Caldwell, Thomas, 1967; UA235.002.053.00005 (Box 53)
  - Calhoun, Noah R., 1955; UA235.002.053.00006 (Box 53)
  - Calvani, Pasquale, 1991; UA235.002.053.00007 (Box 53)
  - Camacho, Laura E., 1983; UA235.002.053.00008 (Box 53)
  - Camerlengo, Henry T., 1970; UA235.002.053.00009 (Box 53)
  - Camelio, Joal D., 1972; UA235.002.053.00010 (Box 53)
  - Cammarata, Paul D., 1982; UA235.002.053.00011 (Box 53)
  - Campagna, Lisa C., 1994; UA235.002.053.00012 (Box 53)
  - Campbell, Paul D. [1 of 2], 1986; UA235.002.053.00013 (Box 53)
  - Campbell, Paul D. [2 of 2], 1986; UA235.002.053.00014 (Box 53)
  - Caporusso, Philip A., 1994; UA235.002.053.00015 (Box 53)
  - Carchidi, Edward, 1965; UA235.002.053.00016 (Box 53)
  - Cardarelli, Joseph A., 1983; UA235.002.053.00017 (Box 53)
  - Cardenas, Cesar H., 2005; UA235.002.053.00018 (Box 53)
  - Cardenas, Luis E., 1992; UA235.002.053.00019 (Box 53)
  - Cargasacchi, John M., 1993; UA235.002.053.00020 (Box 53)
  - Caristi, Richard J., 1972; UA235.002.053.00021 (Box 53)
  - Carlamere, Carl F., 1975; UA235.002.053.00022 (Box 53)
  - Carpenter, John, 1978; UA235.002.053.00023 (Box 53)
  - Carranza, Paola, 2003; UA235.002.053.00024 (Box 53)
  - Carrillo, Roberto, 1978; UA235.002.053.00025 (Box 53)
  - Carro, Odile M., 1995; UA235.002.053.00026 (Box 53)
  - Carter, Michael D., 1994; UA235.002.053.00027 (Box 53)
  - Cartsos, Vassiliki M. [1 of 2], 1994; UA235.002.053.00028 (Box 53)
  - Cartsos, Vassiliki M. [2 of 2], 1996; UA235.002.053.00029 (Box 53)
  - Carvelli, William S., 1956; UA235.002.053.00030 (Box 53)
  - Cashion, Paul David, 1968; UA235.002.053.00031 (Box 53)
  - Castano, Raul, 1994; UA235.002.053.00032 (Box 53)
  - Castellani, Dario, 1986; UA235.002.053.00033 (Box 53)
  - Castillo, Marquita D., 1999; UA235.002.053.00034 (Box 53)
  - Castillo-Ford, Patricia, 1995; UA235.002.053.00035 (Box 53)
  - Castro-Barerra, Carlos, 1983; UA235.002.053.00036 (Box 53)
  - Cataldo, Edmund Jr., 1963; UA235.002.053.00037 (Box 53)
  - Catrambone, Richard J., 1989; UA235.002.053.00038 (Box 53)
  - Caulfield, Zoe, 1984; UA235.002.053.00039 (Box 53)
  - Cavalieri, Robert J., 1979; UA235.002.053.00040 (Box 53)
  - Cavallaro, Carl, 1968; UA235.002.053.00041 (Box 53)
  - Chambliss, Harold T., 2000; UA235.002.053.00042 (Box 53)
  - Cha, Diane Y., 2005; UA235.002.053.00043 (Box 53)
  - Chafka, Abeer [1 of 2], 1998; UA235.002.053.00044 (Box 53)
  - Chafka, Abeer [2 of 2], 1996; UA235.002.053.00045 (Box 53)
  - Chan, William, 1982; UA235.002.053.00046 (Box 53)
  - Chandwani, Brijesh P., 2006; UA235.002.053.00047 (Box 53)
  - Chang, Yu-Shan, 2006; UA235.002.053.00048 (Box 53)
  - Chapman, Brent L., 2000; UA235.002.053.00049 (Box 53)
  - Chapman, Robert, 1974; UA235.002.053.00050 (Box 53)
  - Chapnick, Lorne, 1976; UA235.002.053.00051 (Box 53)
  - Chapra, Anas U. [1 of 2], 1994; UA235.002.053.00052 (Box 53)
  - Chapra, Anas U. [2 of 2], 2001; UA235.002.053.00053 (Box 53)
  - Chapusette, Albert, 1959; UA235.002.053.00054 (Box 53)
  - Chanley, Mark, 1992; UA235.002.053.00055 (Box 53)
  - Charkoudian, George, 1967; UA235.002.053.00056 (Box 53)
  - Charudilaka, Jiraporn, 1981; UA235.002.053.00057 (Box 53)
  - Chartrand, Francois, 1992; UA235.002.053.00058 (Box 53)
  - Chason, Jonathan E., 1999; UA235.002.053.00059 (Box 53)
  - Chawla, Tribhawan N., 1950; UA235.002.053.00060 (Box 53)
  - Cheah, Cheng Kooi, 1954; UA235.002.053.00061 (Box 53)
  - Chen, Bor-Jian, 1986; UA235.002.053.00062 (Box 53)
  - Chen, Chun-Yu, 2002; UA235.002.053.00063 (Box 53)
  - Chen, David T.Y., 1976; UA235.002.053.00064 (Box 53)
  - Chen, Hui-Ling [1 of 2], 2000; UA235.002.053.00065 (Box 53)
  - Chen, Hui-Ling [2 of 2], 2004; UA235.002.053.00066 (Box 53)
  - Chen, Yea-Huey Melody [1 of 2], 1988; UA235.002.053.00067 (Box 53)
  - Chen, Yea-Huey Melody [2 of 2], 1988; UA235.002.053.00068 (Box 53)
  - Chen, Yi-Ju, 2005; UA235.002.053.00069 (Box 53)
  - Chernin, David, 1982; UA235.002.053.00070 (Box 53)
  - Cheung, Wai, 1999; UA235.002.053.00071 (Box 53)
  - Cheylus, Marc Y., 1985; UA235.002.053.00072 (Box 53)
  - Chiang, Theresa, 1967; UA235.002.053.00073 (Box 53)
  - Chiang, Tuze-Wu, 1992; UA235.002.053.00074 (Box 53)
  - Chiminello, Frank J., 1968; UA235.002.053.00075 (Box 53)
  - Chin, Patrick, K.S., 1955; UA235.002.053.00076 (Box 53)
  - Cho, Hyun-Ki, 2000; UA235.002.053.00077 (Box 53)
  - Cho, Il, 2003; UA235.002.053.00078 (Box 53)
  - Choi, Jaeseon, 1996; UA235.002.053.00079 (Box 53)
  - Chow, Kia-Tchao, 1953; UA235.002.054.00001 (Box 54)
  - Chyten, Alan, 1968; UA235.002.054.00002 (Box 54)
  - Chiu, Tsvey-Ching, 1982; UA235.002.054.00003 (Box 54)
  - Claparols, Patricia, 1979; UA235.002.054.00004 (Box 54)
  - Clark, Anthony, 1975; UA235.002.054.00005 (Box 54)
  - Clark, Winston F., 1950; UA235.002.054.00006 (Box 54)
  - Clarke, Antoine B., 1995; UA235.002.054.00007 (Box 54)
  - Clausen, Howard, 1975; UA235.002.054.00008 (Box 54)
  - Coan, Herbert A., 1955; UA235.002.054.00009 (Box 54)
  - Cohen, David I., 1965; UA235.002.054.00010 (Box 54)
  - Cohen, Edward S., 1970; UA235.002.054.00011 (Box 54)
  - Cohen, Gwen S., 1996; UA235.002.054.00012 (Box 54)
  - Cohen, Isaac, 1978; UA235.002.054.00013 (Box 54)
  - Cohen, M. Michael, 1952; UA235.002.054.00014 (Box 54)
  - Cohen-Sasson, Kenneth, 2004; UA235.002.054.00015 (Box 54)
  - Cohen, Patrick, 1980; UA235.002.054.00016 (Box 54)
  - Cohen, Wilfred E., 1950; UA235.002.054.00017 (Box 54)
  - Coiana, Carlo, 1992; UA235.002.054.00018 (Box 54)
  - Colarusso, Carmine A., 1995; UA235.002.054.00019 (Box 54)
  - Cole, Gayla A., 2001; UA235.002.054.00020 (Box 54)
  - Colecchi, Mario H., 1953; UA235.002.054.00021 (Box 54)
  - Collazzo, Robert E., 1984; UA235.002.054.00022 (Box 54)
  - Colle, Albert J., 1949; UA235.002.054.00023 (Box 54)
  - Collins, Robert, 1957; UA235.002.054.00024 (Box 54)
  - Collitro, Michael B., 1948; UA235.002.054.00025 (Box 54)
  - Colt, Socrates G., 1967; UA235.002.054.00026 (Box 54)
  - Colton, Timothy S., 1984; UA235.002.054.00027 (Box 54)
  - Comut, Ali Alper, 2006; UA235.002.054.00028 (Box 54)
  - Contract, Sheldon, 1969; UA235.002.054.00029 (Box 54)
  - Coombs, Robert L., 1952; UA235.002.054.00030 (Box 54)
  - Cooper, Alan E., 1966; UA235.002.054.00031 (Box 54)
  - Cordeiro, Pedrito F. S., 1954; UA235.002.054.00032 (Box 54)
  - Corey, John Bede, 1972; UA235.002.054.00033 (Box 54)
  - Coriat, Paul, 1976; UA235.002.054.00034 (Box 54)
  - Corliss, Steven M., 1988; UA235.002.054.00035 (Box 54)
  - Cornfeld, Robert M., 1957; UA235.002.054.00036 (Box 54)
  - Cortegiano, Louis J., 1970; UA235.002.054.00037 (Box 54)
  - Costanza, Adrian J., 1973; UA235.002.054.00038 (Box 54)
  - Cottrell, David Alden, 1988; UA235.002.054.00039 (Box 54)
  - Coulouriotes, Alexander, 1954; UA235.002.054.00040 (Box 54)
  - Coughlan, Anthony J., 1993; UA235.002.054.00041 (Box 54)
  - Coy, Willard, 1953; UA235.002.054.00042 (Box 54)
  - Coyne, Cathleen P., 1993; UA235.002.054.00043 (Box 54)
  - Cramer, Steven M., 1991; UA235.002.054.00044 (Box 54)
  - Creech, Hadley, 2003; UA235.002.054.00045 (Box 54)
  - Cressman, Peter T., 1972; UA235.002.054.00046 (Box 54)
  - Croll, Burney Michael, 1970; UA235.002.054.00047 (Box 54)
  - Crymes, Thomas G., 1974; UA235.002.054.00048 (Box 54)
  - Cubenas, Julio J., 1996; UA235.002.054.00049 (Box 54)
  - Cullen, Jack M., 1960; UA235.002.054.00050 (Box 54)
  - Culver, Jimmy, 1973; UA235.002.054.00051 (Box 54)
  - Cushner, Leonard, 1951; UA235.002.054.00052 (Box 54)
  - Cushner, Stuart C., 1983; UA235.002.054.00053 (Box 54)
  - Daftary, Fereidoun, 1976; UA235.002.054.00054 (Box 54)
  - Daigle, Jr., Albert, 1973; UA235.002.054.00055 (Box 54)
  - Dajani, Eeman B., 2003; UA235.002.054.00056 (Box 54)
  - Dajani, Eeman B., 2003; UA235.002.054.00057 (Box 54)
  - Dakkak, Iyad, 1991; UA235.002.054.00058 (Box 54)
  - Dalassou, Constantina, 1981; UA235.002.054.00059 (Box 54)
  - Dall'omo, Fabrizio, 1994; UA235.002.054.00060 (Box 54)
  - Daman, Selma T., 1958; UA235.002.054.00061 (Box 54)
  - Damoulis, Peter D., 1989; UA235.002.054.00062 (Box 54)
  - D'amour, Robert P., 1965; UA235.002.054.00063 (Box 54)
  - Danesh, Sanaz, 2001; UA235.002.054.00064 (Box 54)
  - Dano, Armida L., 2002; UA235.002.054.00065 (Box 54)
  - Daryabegi, Yasmin, 1997; UA235.002.054.00066 (Box 54)
  - Dario, Lawrence, 1981; UA235.002.054.00067 (Box 54)
  - Darviche, Jane R., 1987; UA235.002.054.00068 (Box 54)
  - Darviche, Parviz, 1960; UA235.002.054.00069 (Box 54)
  - Darvish, Manouchehr, 1970; UA235.002.054.00070 (Box 54)
  - Darwish, Samia A., 1970; UA235.002.054.00071 (Box 54)
  - Daryabegi, Parviz, 1976; UA235.002.054.00072 (Box 54)
  - Davidson, Herbert, 1956; UA235.002.054.00073 (Box 54)
  - Davis, Leslie, 1978; UA235.002.054.00074 (Box 54)
  - Davis, Nathan T., 1999; UA235.002.054.00075 (Box 54)
  - Davis, Nile M., 1991; UA235.002.054.00076 (Box 54)
  - Davis, W. Morgan, 1968; UA235.002.054.00077 (Box 54)
  - Davis, Stephen R., 1970; UA235.002.054.00078 (Box 54)
  - Day, Gregory N., 1989; UA235.002.054.00079 (Box 54)
  - Dayton, Ralph E., 1969; UA235.002.054.00080 (Box 54)
  - Deangelis, Pasqualle, 1963; UA235.002.054.00081 (Box 54)
  - Deberardinis, Anthony, 1976; UA235.002.054.00082 (Box 54)
  - Deberadinis, Deborah, 1985; UA235.002.054.00083 (Box 54)
  - Decoteau, Jay M., 1986; UA235.002.054.00084 (Box 54)
  - Deemys, George A., 1969; UA235.002.054.00085 (Box 54)
  - DeGarcia, Judith M., 1964; UA235.002.054.00086 (Box 54)
  - Deighan, William, 1983; UA235.002.054.00087 (Box 54)
  - Deitz, Stanley R., 1969; UA235.002.054.00088 (Box 54)
  - Del Castillo, Luis A., 1996; UA235.002.055.00001 (Box 55)
  - Del Castillo, Robert A., 1985; UA235.002.055.00002 (Box 55)
  - Deliperi, Simone, 1999; UA235.002.055.00003 (Box 55)
  - Del Vecchio, Ronald, 1972; UA235.002.055.00004 (Box 55)
  - DeMaio, Aaron A., 2004; UA235.002.055.00005 (Box 55)
  - Denney, Jr., Lawrence, 1970; UA235.002.055.00006 (Box 55)
  - DePaola, Paul F., 1964; UA235.002.055.00007 (Box 55)
  - DeRoche, Joseph H., 1957; UA235.002.055.00008 (Box 55)
  - Derrick, Michael M., 1956; UA235.002.055.00009 (Box 55)
  - Derris, David B., 1964; UA235.002.055.00010 (Box 55)
  - Desantis, Giorgio, 1990; UA235.002.055.00011 (Box 55)
  - Detamore, Robert J., 1954; UA235.002.055.00012 (Box 55)
  - Devine, George, 1965; UA235.002.055.00013 (Box 55)
  - Devitre, Rustam K., 1976; UA235.002.055.00014 (Box 55)
  - Deyampert, Porter L., 1967; UA235.002.055.00015 (Box 55)
  - Dharamshi, Nawaz N., 2002; UA235.002.055.00016 (Box 55)
  - Diamond, Greg R., 1983; UA235.002.055.00017 (Box 55)
  - Diamond, Norman H., 1962; UA235.002.055.00018 (Box 55)
  - Diana, John, 1982; UA235.002.055.00019 (Box 55)
  - Diaz, Jorge C., 1962; UA235.002.055.00020 (Box 55)
  - Diaz-Mendez, Rafael, 1979; UA235.002.055.00021 (Box 55)
  - Dibble, Arthur E., 1960; UA235.002.055.00022 (Box 55)
  - Dibart, Serge N., 1983; UA235.002.055.00023 (Box 55)
  - Di Bonaventura, Orazio, 1982; UA235.002.055.00024 (Box 55)
  - Dicks, Joseph L., 1967; UA235.002.055.00025 (Box 55)
  - Diep, Yek, 2005; UA235.002.055.00026 (Box 55)
  - Dines, Milton, 1960; UA235.002.055.00027 (Box 55)
  - Dion, Michael R., 1995; UA235.002.055.00028 (Box 55)
  - DiBona, Christina, 1991; UA235.002.055.00029 (Box 55)
  - Dischinger, Bill M., 1997; UA235.002.055.00030 (Box 55)
  - DiStasio, Eugene, 1965; UA235.002.055.00031 (Box 55)
  - DiStasio, Joseph, 1955; UA235.002.055.00032 (Box 55)
  - Diversi, Jennifer Irene, 1987; UA235.002.055.00033 (Box 55)
  - Dix, Robert L., 1972; UA235.002.055.00034 (Box 55)
  - Dixter, Charels T., 1972; UA235.002.055.00035 (Box 55)
  - Dobbs, Debra A., 1992; UA235.002.055.00036 (Box 55)
  - Dodelson, Donald J., 1955; UA235.002.055.00037 (Box 55)
  - Dolce, Helene M, 1992; UA235.002.055.00038 (Box 55)
  - Dumas, John J., 1993; UA235.002.055.00039 (Box 55)
  - Doku, Hristo, 1953; UA235.002.055.00040 (Box 55)
  - Donnelly, Jeff E., 1983; UA235.002.055.00041 (Box 55)
  - Donnenfeld, Oscar W., 1960; UA235.002.055.00042 (Box 55)
  - Douglas, Theola, 1981; UA235.002.055.00043 (Box 55)
  - Dossou, Olga, 1989; UA235.002.055.00044 (Box 55)
  - Doswell, John C., 1981; UA235.002.055.00045 (Box 55)
  - Doykos, John D., 1965; UA235.002.055.00046 (Box 55)
  - Drew, Charles, Jr., 1973; UA235.002.055.00047 (Box 55)
  - Driscoll, Leslie H., 1983; UA235.002.055.00048 (Box 55)
  - Drob, Peter L., 1964; UA235.002.055.00049 (Box 55)
  - Duhaime, John E., 1983; UA235.002.055.00050 (Box 55)
  - DuKatz, Lawrence M., 1970; UA235.002.055.00051 (Box 55)
  - Dumas, Armand L., 1960; UA235.002.055.00052 (Box 55)
  - Dumas, Michael, 1956; UA235.002.055.00053 (Box 55)
  - Dunn, Martin J., 1964; UA235.002.055.00054 (Box 55)
  - Duprey, Leo E., Jr., 1958; UA235.002.055.00055 (Box 55)
  - Dwyer, Michael, 1979; UA235.002.055.00056 (Box 55)
  - Dye, Mark, 2004; UA235.002.055.00057 (Box 55)
  - Echeverri, Aurelio, 1961; UA235.002.055.00058 (Box 55)
  - Edalat, Mohammed, 1967; UA235.002.055.00059 (Box 55)
  - Edds, Carl W., 1963; UA235.002.055.00060 (Box 55)
  - Edesess, Robert B., 1966; UA235.002.055.00061 (Box 55)
  - Edmunds, Patrick, 2001; UA235.002.055.00062 (Box 55)
  - Edwards, Carol, 1980; UA235.002.055.00063 (Box 55)
  - Efthimiadis, Nikolaos, 1998; UA235.002.055.00064 (Box 55)
  - Eichner, Marvin, 1981; UA235.002.055.00065 (Box 55)
  - Elahi-Kermani, Sorraya, 1978; UA235.002.055.00066 (Box 55)
  - El-Ebrashi, Mohammed, 1962; UA235.002.055.00067 (Box 55)
  - El-Gendy, Tamer A., 1997; UA235.002.055.00068 (Box 55)
  - El-Hadidy, Mahmoud, 1978; UA235.002.055.00069 (Box 55)
  - El-Kholy, Wessam I., 1993; UA235.002.055.00070 (Box 55)
  - Ellinger, Harley A., 1968; UA235.002.055.00071 (Box 55)
  - Ellison, Jillian E., 1995; UA235.002.055.00072 (Box 55)
  - Ellison, Joseph, 1964; UA235.002.055.00073 (Box 55)
  - Elkadry, Noah A., 1994; UA235.002.056.00001 (Box 56)
  - Elmalt, Magda Ahmed, 1985; UA235.002.056.00002 (Box 56)
  - Elmi, Paula, 2004; UA235.002.056.00003 (Box 56)
  - Englander, Abraham, 1973; UA235.002.056.00004 (Box 56)
  - Errera, Marc M., 1987; UA235.002.056.00005 (Box 56)
  - Erwich, David, 1966; UA235.002.056.00006 (Box 56)
  - Estabrooks, Lewis N., 1969; UA235.002.056.00007 (Box 56)
  - Estrada, Swanny, 1996; UA235.002.056.00008 (Box 56)
  - Etienne, Daniel, 1977; UA235.002.056.00009 (Box 56)
  - Evans, George, 1965; UA235.002.056.00010 (Box 56)
  - Fabara, Hector, 1951; UA235.002.056.00011 (Box 56)
  - Failla, Francesca, 1999; UA235.002.056.00012 (Box 56)
  - Faith, Robert W., 1958; UA235.002.056.00013 (Box 56)
  - Fakitsas, John C., 1982; UA235.002.056.00014 (Box 56)
  - Fantaci, Arthur, 1952; UA235.002.056.00015 (Box 56)
  - Farnham, John, 1962; UA235.002.056.00016 (Box 56)
  - Farren, Patrick J., 1983; UA235.002.056.00017 (Box 56)
  - Fayad, Tarek, 1999; UA235.002.056.00018 (Box 56)
  - Feldman, Joseph, 1963; UA235.002.056.00019 (Box 56)
  - Feldman, Steven, 1970; UA235.002.056.00020 (Box 56)
  - Feliciano-Nieves, Lourdes, 1983; UA235.002.056.00021 (Box 56)
  - Feller, Joseph P., 2003; UA235.002.056.00022 (Box 56)
  - Ferdianakis, Konstantinos, 1997; UA235.002.056.00023 (Box 56)
  - Ferdianakis, Constantinos E., 1995; UA235.002.056.00024 (Box 56)
  - Ferrandiz, Jose, 1983; UA235.002.056.00025 (Box 56)
  - Ferraro, Louis A., 1986; UA235.002.056.00026 (Box 56)
  - Ferreira, Susana, 2000; UA235.002.056.00027 (Box 56)
  - Ferriol, Maria, 2003; UA235.002.056.00028 (Box 56)
  - Fettouh, Ahmed Ibrahim, 2000; UA235.002.056.00029 (Box 56)
  - Fields, David S., 1972; UA235.002.056.00030 (Box 56)
  - Fields, Jason, 2001; UA235.002.056.00031 (Box 56)
  - Fields, John, 1976; UA235.002.056.00032 (Box 56)
  - Fields, Robert S, 1956; UA235.002.056.00033 (Box 56)
  - Filandrianos, Angela, 1986; UA235.002.056.00034 (Box 56)
  - Filipowicz, Francis, 1962; UA235.002.056.00035 (Box 56)
  - Fine, Gerald, 1978; UA235.002.056.00036 (Box 56)
  - Finamore, Paul R., 1996; UA235.002.056.00037 (Box 56)
  - Finkle, Philip D., 1951; UA235.002.056.00038 (Box 56)
  - Finn, John J., 1962; UA235.002.056.00039 (Box 56)
  - Finocchiaro, Donna T., 1996; UA235.002.056.00040 (Box 56)
  - Fiore, William, 1976; UA235.002.056.00041 (Box 56)
  - Fister, Carey, 2003; UA235.002.056.00042 (Box 56)
  - Fitzgerald, Paul D., 1996; UA235.002.056.00043 (Box 56)
  - Frankell, Bennett, 1970; UA235.002.056.00044 (Box 56)
  - Fleisher, Ronda S., 2001; UA235.002.056.00045 (Box 56)
  - Flood, James E., 1978; UA235.002.056.00046 (Box 56)
  - Fontaine, Claude L, 1987; UA235.002.056.00047 (Box 56)
  - Font-Buxo, Jose, 1960; UA235.002.056.00048 (Box 56)
  - Fooks, Elina, 2001; UA235.002.056.00049 (Box 56)
  - Fooladi, Baharak, 2003; UA235.002.056.00050 (Box 56)
  - Foote, George B., 1950; UA235.002.056.00051 (Box 56)
  - Ford, James E., 1962; UA235.002.056.00052 (Box 56)
  - Forgosh, Jeffrey, 1974; UA235.002.056.00053 (Box 56)
  - Foster, Samuel C., 1970; UA235.002.056.00054 (Box 56)
  - Foulke, Clark N., 1967; UA235.002.056.00055 (Box 56)
  - Frankel, Charles Jay, 1970; UA235.002.056.00056 (Box 56)
  - Frankel, Martin E., 1962; UA235.002.056.00057 (Box 56)
  - Frankel, Spencer N., 1959; UA235.002.056.00058 (Box 56)
  - Fraternale, Paolo, 1990; UA235.002.056.00059 (Box 56)
  - Frazzato, Reginald, 1957; UA235.002.056.00060 (Box 56)
  - Freedman, Cyril, 1971; UA235.002.056.00061 (Box 56)
  - Freeman, Norman A., 1953; UA235.002.056.00062 (Box 56)
  - Fridley, Harry H, 1950; UA235.002.056.00063 (Box 56)
  - Fried, Neil, 1979; UA235.002.056.00064 (Box 56)
  - Friedman, Charles, 1957; UA235.002.056.00065 (Box 56)
  - Friedman, Harold, 1952; UA235.002.056.00066 (Box 56)
  - Fried, Kenneth, 1951; UA235.002.056.00067 (Box 56)
  - Frim, Bernard J, 1968; UA235.002.056.00068 (Box 56)
  - Frim, Sumner P, 1974; UA235.002.056.00069 (Box 56)
  - Frontera-Philippi, Miguel, 1987; UA235.002.056.00070 (Box 56)
  - Frost, Steven L., 1992; UA235.002.056.00071 (Box 56)
  - Frutchey, Brian, 2000; UA235.002.056.00072 (Box 56)
  - Fu, Alexander S., 1995; UA235.002.056.00073 (Box 56)
  - Funakoshi, Eiji, 1971; UA235.002.056.00074 (Box 56)
  - Furman, Zui, 1977; UA235.002.056.00075 (Box 56)
  - Furtado, Maria, 1981; UA235.002.056.00076 (Box 56)
  - Gabe, Timothy M, 1983; UA235.002.057.00001 (Box 57)
  - Galen, Ralph, 1951; UA235.002.057.00002 (Box 57)
  - Gaillard, Michele, 1974; UA235.002.057.00003 (Box 57)
  - Gale, Joel, 1994; UA235.002.057.00004 (Box 57)